Guide to the William Hewlett Papers M1995
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 2: Financial, 1945-2008
  - Subseries B: Philanthropy and Gifts, 1958-2001
    - Cash Contributions (1984) (part 2 of 2), 1983-1985 (Box 171, Folder 5)
    - Cash Contributions (1985), 1985-1986 (Box 172, Folder 1)
    - Cash Contributions (1986) (part 1 of 3), 1985-1987 (Box 172, Folder 2)
      Includes correspondence and photographs of a school in Africa.
    - Cash Contributions (1986) (part 2 of 3), 1985-1987 (Box 172, Folder 3)
    - Cash Contributions (1986) (part 3 of 3), 1985-1987 (Box 172, Folder 4)
    - Cash Contributions (1987) (part 1 of 2), 1986-1988 (Box 172, Folder 5)
    - Cash Contributions (1987) (part 2 of 2), 1986-1988 (Box 172, Folder 6)
    - Cash Contributions (1988) (part 1 of 2), 1987-1990 (Box 173, Folder 1)
    - Cash Contributions (1988) (part 2 of 2), 1987-1990 (Box 173, Folder 2)
    - Cash Contributions (1989) (part 1 of 2), 1988-1990 (Box 173, Folder 3)
    - Cash Contributions (1989) (part 2 of 2), 1988-1990 (Box 173, Folder 4)
    - Cash Contributions (1990) (part 1 of 3), 1989-1991 (Box 173, Folder 5)
    - Cash Contributions (1990) (part 2 of 3), 1989-1991 (Box 174, Folder 1)
    - Cash Contributions (1990) (part 3 of 3), 1989-1991 (Box 174, Folder 2)
    - Cash Contributions (1991) (part 1 of 2), 1990-1992 (Box 174, Folder 3)
    - Cash Contributions (1991) (part 2 of 2), 1990-1992 (Box 174, Folder 4)
    - Cash Contributions (1992) (part 1 of 4), 1991-1993 (Box 174, Folder 5)
    - Cash Contributions (1992) (part 2 of 4), 1991-1993 (Box 174, Folder 6)
    - Cash Contributions (1992) (part 3 of 4), 1991-1993 (Box 175, Folder 1)
    - Cash Contributions (1992) (part 4 of 4), 1991-1993 (Box 175, Folder 2)
    - Cash Contributions (1993) (part 1 of 5), 1992-1994 (Box 175, Folder 3)
    - Cash Contributions (1993) (part 2 of 5), 1992-1994 (Box 175, Folder 4)
      Includes correspondence, financial paperwork, ephemera, and 2 cuff links sent as a gift by the Tahoe Forest Hospital Foundation.
    - Cash Contributions (1993) (part 3 of 5), 1992-1994 (Box 175, Folder 5)
    - Cash Contributions (1993) (part 4 of 5), 1992-1994 (Box 175, Folder 6)
    - Cash Contributions (1993) (part 5 of 5), 1992-1994 (Box 176, Folder 1)
    - Cash Contributions (1994) (part 1 of 14), 1993-1995 (Box 176, Folder 2)
      Includes correspondence, a photograph of a planned building, a pin and sticker sent as a gift from Delta Waterfowl, and other supplemental material.
    - Cash Contributions (1994) (part 2 of 14), 1993-1995 (Box 176, Folder 3)
    - Cash Contributions (1994) (part 3 of 14), 1993-1995 (Box 176, Folder 4)
    - Cash Contributions (1994) (part 4 of 14), 1993-1995 (Box 176, Folder 5)
      Includes correspondence, financial paperwork, and a pin and sticker sent as a gift from Delta Waterfowl.
    - Cash Contributions (1994) (part 5 of 14), 1993-1995 (Box 176, Folder 6)
    - Cash Contributions (1994) (part 6 of 14), 1993-1995 (Box 177, Folder 1)
      Includes correspondence and photographs of the World Affairs Center in San Francisco.
    - Cash Contributions (1994) (part 7 of 14), 1993-1995 (Box 177, Folder 2)
    - Cash Contributions (1994) (part 8 of 14), 1993-1995 (Box 177, Folder 3)
    - Cash Contributions (1994) (part 9 of 14), 1993-1995 (Box 177, Folder 4)
    - Cash Contributions (1994) (part 10 of 14), 1993-1995 (Box 177, Folder 5)
    - Cash Contributions (1994) (part 11 of 14), 1993-1995 (Box 177, Folder 6)
    - Cash Contributions (1994) (part 12 of 14), 1993-1995 (Box 178, Folder 1)
    - Cash Contributions (1994) (part 13 of 14), 1993-1995 (Box 178, Folder 2)
    - Cash Contributions (1994) (part 14 of 14), 1993-1995 (Box 178, Folder 3)
    - Cash Contributions (January-March 1995) (part 1 of 2), 1995-1996 (Box 178, Folder 4)
    - Cash Contributions (January-March 1995) (part 2 of 2), 1995-1996 (Box 178, Folder 5)
    - Cash Contributions (April-June 1995) (part 1 of 4), 1994-1996 (Box 178, Folder 6)
    - Cash Contributions (April-June 1995) (part 2 of 4), 1994-1996 (Box 178, Folder 7)
    - Cash Contributions (April-June 1995) (part 3 of 4), 1994-1996 (Box 179, Folder 1)
    - Cash Contributions (April-June 1995) (part 4 of 4), 1994-1996 (Box 179, Folder 2)
    - Cash Contributions (July-September 1995) (part 1 of 2), 1995-1996 (Box 179, Folder 3)
    - Cash Contributions (July-September 1995) (part 2 of 2), 1995-1996 (Box 179, Folder 4)
    - Cash Contributions (October-December 1995) (part 1 of 4), 1995-1996 (Box 179, Folder 5)
    - Cash Contributions (October-December 1995) (part 2 of 4), 1995-1996 (Box 180, Folder 1)
    - Cash Contributions (October-December 1995) (part 3 of 4), 1995-1996 (Box 180, Folder 2)
    - Cash Contributions (October-December 1995) (part 4 of 4), 1995-1996 (Box 180, Folder 3)
    - Cash Contributions (January-March 1996) (part 1 of 3), 1994-1997 (Box 180, Folder 4)
    - Cash Contributions (January-March 1996) (part 2 of 3), 1994-1997 (Box 180, Folder 5)
    - Cash Contributions (January-March 1996) (part 3 of 3), 1994-1997 (Box 181, Folder 1)
    - Cash Contributions (April-June 1996) (part 1 of 4), 1996-1998 (Box 181, Folder 2)
    - Cash Contributions (April-June 1996) (part 2 of 4), 1996-1998 (Box 181, Folder 3)
    - Cash Contributions (April-June 1996) (part 3 of 4), 1996-1998 (Box 181, Folder 4)
    - Cash Contributions (April-June 1996) (part 4 of 4), 1996-1998 (Box 182, Folder 1)
    - Cash Contributions (July-September 1996) (part 1 of 2), 1996-1997 (Box 182, Folder 2)
    - Cash Contributions (July-September 1996) (part 2 of 2), 1996-1997 (Box 182, Folder 3)
    - Cash Contributions (October-December 1996) (part 1 of 4), 1996-1998 (Box 182, Folder 4)
    - Cash Contributions (October-December 1996) (part 2 of 4), 1996-1998 (Box 183, Folder 1)
    - Cash Contributions (October-December 1996) (part 3 of 4), 1996-1998 (Box 183, Folder 2)
    - Cash Contributions (October-December 1996) (part 4 of 4), 1996-1998 (Box 183, Folder 3)
    - Cash Contributions (January-March 1997) (part 1 of 4), 1996-1997 (Box 183, Folder 4)
    - Cash Contributions (January-March 1997) (part 2 of 4), 1996-1997 (Box 183, Folder 5)
    - Cash Contributions (January-March 1997) (part 3 of 4), 1996-1997 (Box 183, Folder 6)
    - Cash Contributions (January-March 1997) (part 4 of 4), 1996-1997 (Box 184, Folder 1)
    - Cash Contributions (April-June 1997) (part 1 of 3), 1997-1998 (Box 184, Folder 2)
    - Cash Contributions (April-June 1997) (part 2 of 3), 1997-1998 (Box 184, Folder 3)
    - Cash Contributions (April-June 1997) (part 3 of 3), 1997-1998 (Box 184, Folder 4)
    - Cash Contributions (July-September 1997) (part 1 of 4) (Box 184, Folder 5)
    - Cash Contributions (July-September 1997) (part 2 of 4) (Box 184, Folder 6)
    - Cash Contributions (July-September 1997) (part 3 of 4) (Box 184, Folder 7)
    - Cash Contributions (July-September 1997) (part 4 of 4) (Box 185, Folder 1)
    - Cash Contributions (October-December 1997) (part 1 of 3), 1997-1998 (Box 185, Folder 2)
    - Cash Contributions (October-December 1997) (part 2 of 3), 1997-1998 (Box 185, Folder 3)
    - Cash Contributions (October-December 1997) (part 3 of 3), 1997-1998 (Box 185, Folder 4)
    - Cash Contributions (1998) (part 1 of 6), 1997-1999 (Box 185, Folder 5)
    - Cash Contributions (1998) (part 2 of 6), 1997-1998 (Box 185, Folder 6)
    - Cash Contributions (1998) (part 3 of 6), 1997-1999 (Box 186, Folder 1)
    - Cash Contributions (1998) (part 4 of 6), 1997-1999 (Box 186, Folder 2)
    - Cash Contributions (1998) (part 5 of 6), 1997-1999 (Box 186, Folder 3)
    - Cash Contributions (1998) (part 6 of 6), 1997-1999 (Box 186, Folder 4)
    - Cash Contributions (1999) (part 1 of 2), 1999-2000 (Box 186, Folder 5)
    - Cash Contributions (1999) (part 2 of 2), 1999-2000 (Box 187, Folder 1)
    - Cash Contributions (2000) (part 1 of 7), 1999-2002 (Box 187, Folder 2)
    - Cash Contributions (2000) (part 2 of 7), 1999-2002 (Box 187, Folder 3)
    - Cash Contributions (2000) (part 3 of 7), 1999-2002 (Box 187, Folder 4)
    - Cash Contributions (2000) (part 4 of 7), 1999-2002 (Box 188, Folder 1)
    - Cash Contributions (2000) (part 5 of 7), 1999-2002 (Box 188, Folder 2)
    - Cash Contributions (2000) (part 6 of 7), 1999-2002 (Box 188, Folder 3)
    - Cash Contributions (2000) (part 7 of 7), 1999-2002 (Box 188, Folder 4)
    - Catholic University of America, 1989-1992 (Box 188, Folder 5)
    - Catholic University of America, 1992-1993 (Box 188, Folder 6)
    - Center for Excellence in Nonprofits, 1996, undated (Box 189, Folder 1)
    - Center to Prevent Handgun Violence, 1991-1998 (Box 189, Folder 2)
    - Charitable File, 1990-1992 (Box 189, Folder 3)
    - Charitable File, 1992-1993 (Box 189, Folder 4)
    - Children's Health Council, 1993-1997 (Box 189, Folder 5)
    - Christmas Gifts Given, 1976-1992 (Box 189, Folder 6)
    - Colby College Museum of Art, 1996-1999 (Box 189, Folder 7)
    - Commitment Recap, 1993-1999 (Box 189, Folder 8)
    - Common Cause, 1993-1995 (Box 189, Folder 9)
    - Community Association for Rehabilitation, 1996 (Box 189, Folder 10)
    - Community Foundation of Santa Clara County, 1986-1996 (Box 189, Folder 11)
    - Community Foundation Silicon Valley, 1997 (Box 189, Folder 12)
    - Conservation International (part 1 of 2), 1993-1995 (Box 189, Folder 13)
    - Conservation International (part 2 of 2), 1993-1995 (Box 190, Folder 1)
    - Conservation International, 1996-2001 (Box 190, Folder 2)
    - Contributions Made, 1992 (Box 190, Folder 3)
    - Contributions to Stanford, 1970-1971 (Box 190, Folder 4)
    - Contributions to Stanford, 1972 (Box 190, Folder 5)
    - Contributions to Stanford, 1973-1974 (Box 190, Folder 6)
    - Contributions to Stanford, 1974-1975 (Box 190, Folder 7)
    - Contributions to Stanford, 1976-1977 (Box 190, Folder 8)
    - Contributions, Donations, and Pledges, 1960-1961 (Box 190, Folder 9)
    - Contributions: A-D, 1998-2000 (Box 190, Folder 10)
    - Contributions: E-I, 1998-1999 (Box 191, Folder 1)
    - Contributions: J-M, 1998-2000 (Box 191, Folder 2)
    - Contributions: N-R, 1998-2000 (Box 191, Folder 3)
    - Contributions: S-Z, 1998-2000 (Box 191, Folder 4)
    - Contributions: Chronological, 1992-1994 (Box 191, Folder 5)
    - Contributions: Chronological (part 1 of 2), 1995 (Box 191, Folder 6)
    - Contributions: Chronological (part 2 of 2), 1995 (Box 192, Folder 1)
    - Contributions: Chronological (part 1 of 2), 1996 (Box 192, Folder 2)
    - Contributions: Chronological (part 2 of 2), 1996 (Box 192, Folder 3)
    - Contributions: Chronological (part 1 of 2), 1997 (Box 192, Folder 4)
    - Contributions: Chronological (part 2 of 2), 1997 (Box 192, Folder 5)
    - Contributions: Major Donor Filing Rules (part 1 of 4), 1988-1996 (Box 192, Folder 6)
    - Contributions: Major Donor Filing Rules (part 2 of 4), 1988-1996 (Box 192, Folder 7)
    - Contributions: Major Donor Filing Rules (part 3 of 4), 1988-1996 (Box 193, Folder 1)
    - Contributions: Major Donor Filing Rules (part 4 of 4), 1988-1996 (Box 193, Folder 2)
    - Contributions: No Action Taken, 1967 (Box 193, Folder 3)
    - Contributions: No Action Taken, 1969-1970 (Box 193, Folder 4)
    - Contributions: No Action Taken, 1971 (Box 193, Folder 5)
    - Contributions: No Action Taken, 1972 (Box 193, Folder 6)
    - Cyrus and Susan Mills Society, 1998-1999 (Box 193, Folder 7)
    - Del Mar High School, 1995 (Box 193, Folder 8)
    - Delta Waterfowl Foundation, 1998 (Box 193, Folder 9)
    - El Camino Hospital Foundation, 1984-1993 (Box 193, Folder 10)
    - Exploratorium: 2 to 1 Match, 1990 (Box 193, Folder 11)
    - Exploratorium: General (part 1 of 2), 1984-1992 (Box 193, Folder 12)
    - Exploratorium: General (part 2 of 2), 1984-1992 (Box 193, Folder 13)
    - Exploratorium: General, 1992-1998 (Box 194, Folder 1)
    - Filings for 501(c)3, 1983-1999 (Box 194, Folder 2)
    - First Presbyterian Church, 1958 (Box 194, Folder 3)
    - First Presbyterian Church (part 1 of 3), 1983-2000 (Box 194, Folder 4)
    - First Presbyterian Church (part 2 of 3), 1983-2000 (Box 194, Folder 5)
    - First Presbyterian Church (part 3 of 3), 1983-2000 (Box 194, Folder 6)
    - Flora Family Foundation: Annual Report (1999), 2000 (Box 194, Folder 7)
    - Franciscan University of Steubenville, 1984-1985 (Box 194, Folder 8)
    - Friends of the Children's Theatre of Palo Alto, 1986-1987, 1998 (Box 194, Folder 9)
    - Gifts, 1978-1981 (Box 194, Folder 10)
    - Gifts, 1980-1987 (Box 194, Folder 11)
    - Gifts, 1991 (Box 194, Folder 12)
    - Gifts, 1992-1997 (Box 194, Folder 13)
    - Gifts to Bradford Family, 1981-1991 (Box 195, Folder 1)
    - Gifts to Family (part 1 of 2), 1992-1993 (Box 195, Folder 2)
    - Gifts to Family (part 2 of 2), 1992-1993 (Box 195, Folder 3)
    - Gifts to Hewlett Family, 1983-1985 (Box 195, Folder 4)
    - Gifts to Menlo College, William and Flora Hewlett Foundation, Stanford University, San Francisco Opera, and SETI (1978-2001), 1997-2001 (Box 195, Folder 5)
    - Gifts Under $1,000, Over $1,000, and from Rosemary Hewlett (1977-1999) (part 1 of 3) (Box 195, Folder 6)
    - Gifts Under $1,000, Over $1,000, and from Rosemary Hewlett (1977-1999) (part 2 of 3) (Box 195, Folder 7)
    - Gifts Under $1,000, Over $1,000, and from Rosemary Hewlett (1977-1999) (part 3 of 3) (Box 195, Folder 8)
    - Global Fund for Women, 1989-1990 (Box 195, Folder 9)
    - Global Fund for Women, 1995 (Box 195, Folder 10)
    - Golden California Society, 1996 (Box 195, Folder 11)
    - Golden Drift Historical Society, 1989-1991 (Box 195, Folder 12)
    - Graduate Theological Union: Contributions, 1974-1985 (Box 195, Folder 13)
    - Graduate Theological Union: General (part 1 of 3), 1979-1989 (Box 196, Folder 1)
    - Graduate Theological Union: General (part 2 of 3), 1979-1989 (Box 196, Folder 2)
    - Graduate Theological Union: General (part 3 of 3), 1979-1989 (Box 196, Folder 3)
    - Graduate Theological Union: General, 1993-1999 (Box 196, Folder 4)
    - Graduate Theological Union: Library Dedication, 1986-1993 (Box 196, Folder 5)
    - Graduate Theological Union: Robert M. Barr Meeting, 1990-1991 (Box 196, Folder 6)
    - Handgun Control Incorporated, 1990-1992 (Box 196, Folder 7)
    - Harvard University, 1994-1998 (Box 196, Folder 8)
    - Hewlett Family Scholarship, 1984 (Box 196, Folder 9)
    - Hewlett-Packard Committee for Good Government, 1993-1996 (Box 196, Folder 10)
    - Hewlett-Packard Matching Gift Program, 1994 (Box 196, Folder 11)
    - Hiller Museum of Northern California Aviation, 1996-1998 (Box 196, Folder 12)
    - Hoover Institution on War, Peace and Revolution: Annual Report, 1988-1989 (Box 496, Folder 1)
    - Hoover Institution on War, Peace and Revolution: Annual Report, 1990 (Box 496, Folder 2)
    - Hoover Institution on War, Peace and Revolution: Annual Report, 1992-1993 (Box 496, Folder 3)
    - Hoover Institution on War, Peace and Revolution: Annual Report, 1994-1995 (Box 496, Folder 4)
    - Hoover Institution on War, Peace and Revolution: Annual Report, 1996 (Box 496, Folder 5)
    - Hoover Institution on War, Peace and Revolution: Correspondence, 1986-1988 (Box 496, Folder 6)
    - Hoover Institution on War, Peace and Revolution: Correspondence, 1991-1994 (Box 496, Folder 7)
    - Hoover Institution on War, Peace and Revolution: Correspondence, 1995-2001 (Box 497, Folder 1)
    - Hoover Institution on War, Peace and Revolution: Hoover Digest, 1998 (Box 497, Folder 2)
    - Hoover Institution on War, Peace and Revolution: Newsletters, 1993-1998 (Box 497, Folder 3)
    - Hoover Institution on War, Peace and Revolution: Viewpoints, 1993-1998 (Box 497, Folder 4)
    - Hospital House, 1982 (Box 196, Folder 13)
    - International Foundation for Education and Self-Help (part 1 of 7), 1988-1998 (Box 196, Folder 14)
    - International Foundation for Education and Self-Help (part 2 of 7), 1988-1998 (Box 197, Folder 1)
    - International Foundation for Education and Self-Help (part 3 of 7), 1988-1998 (Box 197, Folder 2)
    - International Foundation for Education and Self-Help (part 4 of 7), 1988-1998 (Box 197, Folder 3)
    - International Foundation for Education and Self-Help (part 5 of 7), 1988-1998 (Box 197, Folder 4)
    - International Foundation for Education and Self-Help (part 6 of 7), 1988-1998 (Box 197, Folder 5)
    - International Foundation for Education and Self-Help (part 7 of 7), 1988-1998 (Box 198, Folder 1)
    - Johns Hopkins University, 1996 (Box 198, Folder 2)
    - Jordan Society, 1992 (Box 198, Folder 3)
      Includes correspondence with Najeeb Halaby, a speech by Queen Noor of Jordan, and annual reports.
    - Junior Achievement International, 1988-1994 (Box 198, Folder 4)
    - Junior Achievement International, 1996-2000 (Box 198, Folder 5)
    - Kenyon College, 1980-1993 (Box 198, Folder 6)
    - Kenyon College, 1995-1997 (Box 198, Folder 7)
    - KQED: Capital Fund, 1988-1991 (Box 198, Folder 8)
    - KQED: General, 1995-1997 (Box 198, Folder 9)
    - League to Save Lake Tahoe, 1974-1998 (Box 198, Folder 10)
    - Lowell High School: General (part 1 of 3), 1980-2001 (Box 199, Folder 1)
    - Lowell High School: General (part 2 of 3), 1980-2001 (Box 199, Folder 2)
    - Lowell High School: General (part 3 of 3), 1980-2001 (Box 199, Folder 3)
    - Lowell High School: Grant for Computer Equipment, 1996-1997 (Box 199, Folder 4)
    - Lytton Gardens: Community Housing, 1983 (Box 199, Folder 5)
    - Lytton Gardens: Health Care Center, 1980-1984 (Box 199, Folder 6)
    - Mackay Senior Citizens Center and Clinic, 1992-1995 (Box 199, Folder 7)
    - Marquette University: General, 1986-1993 (Box 199, Folder 8)
    - Marquette University: General, 1993-1995 (Box 199, Folder 9)
    - Marquette University: Thank You Letters, 1986-1994 (Box 199, Folder 10)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology: Edgerton Center, 1993-1995 (Box 200, Folder 1)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology: General, 1971-1982 (Box 200, Folder 2)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology: General (part 1 of 4), 1984-1999 (Box 200, Folder 3)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology: General (part 2 of 4), 1984-1999 (Box 200, Folder 4)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology: General (part 3 of 4), 1984-1999 (Box 200, Folder 5)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology: General (part 4 of 4), 1984-1999 (Box 200, Folder 6)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology: Stratton Chair, 1979-1986 (Box 200, Folder 7)
    - Menlo School and College: 1 to 1 Matching, 1996-1997 (Box 200, Folder 8)
    - Menlo School and College: General (part 1 of 4), 1980-1996 (Box 200, Folder 9)
    - Menlo School and College: General (part 2 of 4), 1980-1996 (Box 201, Folder 1)
    - Menlo School and College: General (part 3 of 4), 1980-1996 (Box 201, Folder 2)
    - Menlo School and College: General (part 4 of 4), 1980-1996 (Box 201, Folder 3)
    - Menlo School and College: Hewlett-Packard Equipment, 1993-1996 (Box 201, Folder 4)
    - Mills College: 2 to 1 Challenge, 1989-1995 (Box 201, Folder 5)
    - Mills College: General, 1984-1987 (Box 201, Folder 6)
    - Mills College: General, 1988-1990 (Box 201, Folder 7)
    - Mills College: General, 1991-1996 (Box 201, Folder 8)
    - Minnesota Public Radio, 1995-1997 (Box 201, Folder 9)
    - Miramonte Mental Health Services, 1976 (Box 201, Folder 10)
    - Monterey Bay Aquarium, 1994-1996 (Box 201, Folder 11)
    - Monterey Bay Aquarium, 1996-1998 (Box 201, Folder 12)
    - Monterey Institute for Research in Astronomy (part 1 of 2), 1981-1989 (Box 202, Folder 1)
    - Monterey Institute for Research in Astronomy (part 2 of 2), 1981-1989 (Box 202, Folder 2)
    - Monterey Institute for Research in Astronomy, 1990-2000 (Box 202, Folder 3)
    - Moritz Community Hospital, 1985 (Box 202, Folder 4)
    - National Academy of Sciences, 1990-1995 (Box 202, Folder 5)
    - Nature Conservancy, 1982-1986 (Box 202, Folder 6)
    - Nature Conservancy, 1986-1989 (Box 202, Folder 7)
    - Nature Conservancy, 1990-2001 (Box 202, Folder 8)
    - New Children's Shelter Fund, 1989-1995 (Box 202, Folder 9)
    - Non-Cash Contributions, 1996 (Box 202, Folder 10)
    - North American Wildlife Foundation, 1987-1992 (Box 203, Folder 1)
    - Opportunities Industrialization Corporation West, 1978-1982 (Box 203, Folder 2)
    - Opportunities Industrialization Corporation West (part 1 of 3), 1985-1991 (Box 203, Folder 3)
      Includes correspondence and photographs, some of Hewlett attending an event.
    - Opportunities Industrialization Corporation West (part 2 of 3), 1985-1991 (Box 203, Folder 4)
    - Opportunities Industrialization Corporation West (part 3 of 3), 1985-1991 (Box 203, Folder 5)
    - Opportunities Industrialization Corporation West, 1991-1994 (Box 203, Folder 6)
    - Opportunities Industrialization Corporation West, 1998-1999 (Box 203, Folder 7)
    - Overseas Development Council, 1995 (Box 203, Folder 8)
    - Owl Trust, 1998 (Box 203, Folder 9)
    - Palo Alto Centennial Fund, 1993-1994 (Box 203, Folder 10)
    - Palo Alto Medical Foundation, 1981-1983 (Box 203, Folder 11)
    - Palo Alto Medical Foundation, 1984-1990 (Box 203, Folder 12)
    - Palo Alto Medical Foundation, 1992-1995 (Box 204, Folder 1)
    - Peninsula Community Foundation for the Truckee/Donner/North Lake Tahoe Community Foundation Fund, 1998 (Box 204, Folder 2)
    - Peninsula Open Space Trust, 1996 (Box 204, Folder 3)
    - Planned Parenthood, 1982-1983 (Box 204, Folder 4)
    - Policy for Annual Gifts to Family, 1998-2000 (Box 204, Folder 5)
    - Property Contributions, 1995-1996 (Box 204, Folder 6)
    - Property Contributions, 1997 (Box 204, Folder 7)
    - Psoriasis Research Institute, 1993-1994 (Box 204, Folder 8)
    - Raphael House, 1982 (Box 204, Folder 9)
    - Requests for Assistance Turned Down, 1972-1973 (Box 204, Folder 10)
    - Requests for Assistance Turned Down, 1978 (Box 204, Folder 11)
    - Requests for Assistance Turned Down, 1981-1983 (Box 204, Folder 12)
    - Requests for Assistance Turned Down (part 1 of 2), 1983-1985 (Box 204, Folder 13)
    - Requests for Assistance Turned Down (part 2 of 2), 1983-1985 (Box 204, Folder 14)
    - Requests for Assistance Turned Down (part 1 of 3), 1986-1987 (Box 204, Folder 15)
    - Requests for Assistance Turned Down (part 2 of 3), 1985-1987 (Box 205, Folder 1)
    - Requests for Assistance Turned Down (part 3 of 3), 1985-1987 (Box 205, Folder 2)
    - Requests for Assistance Turned Down, 1987-1988 (Box 205, Folder 3)
    - Requests for Assistance Turned Down, 1988-1989 (Box 205, Folder 4)
    - Requests for Assistance Turned Down, 1989-1991 (Box 206, Folder 1)
    - Requests for Assistance Turned Down, 1991-1992 (Box 206, Folder 2)
    - Requests for Assistance Turned Down, 1992-1993 (Box 206, Folder 3)
    - Requests for Assistance Turned Down (part 1 of 2), 1993-1994 (Box 206, Folder 4)
    - Requests for Assistance Turned Down (part 2 of 2), 1993-1994 (Box 206, Folder 5)
    - Requests for Assistance Turned Down (part 1 of 3), 1994-1995 (Box 206, Folder 6)
    - Requests for Assistance Turned Down (part 2 of 3), 1994-1995 (Box 207, Folder 1)
    - Requests for Assistance Turned Down (part 3 of 3), 1994-1995 (Box 207, Folder 2)
    - Requests for Assistance Turned Down (part 1 of 2), 1996 (Box 207, Folder 3)
    - Requests for Assistance Turned Down (part 2 of 2), 1996 (Box 207, Folder 4)
    - Requests for Assistance Turned Down (part 1 of 4), 1997 (Box 207, Folder 5)
    - Requests for Assistance Turned Down (part 2 of 4), 1997 (Box 208, Folder 1)
    - Requests for Assistance Turned Down (part 3 of 4), 1997 (Box 208, Folder 2)
    - Requests for Assistance Turned Down (part 4 of 4), 1997 (Box 208, Folder 3)
    - Requests for Assistance Turned Down (part 1 of 5), 1998 (Box 208, Folder 4)
    - Requests for Assistance Turned Down (part 2 of 5), 1998 (Box 209, Folder 1)